Dana J. PaQuet

7250 Moller Ave St. Louis, MO 63143 (314)707-2224 danapaquet@gmail.com

Professional Objective

Current student in LaunchCode seeking to build on and expand my growing skills in computer science and programming. I am eager to work in a position that is challenging and will fulfill my desire to learn and grow. Have gai Service-oriented professional with 9 years with extensive experience in hiring and training staff, customer service, cost management, and loss prevention.

Skills

- Self motivated
- Organized
- Management experience
- Inventory management
- Gaining experience in programming languages such as Java & Python
- Building familiarity with Spring, Hibernate, and Thymeleaf

Work History

Kitchen Manager

Seed Sprout Spoon - 3137 Morganford Rd Saint Louis, MO 63116

March 2017 - Present

- Maintains proper guidelines to insure food safety and freshness
- Follows standardized recipes and procedures
- Prepares and packages daily menu items
- Works to insure the standard for high quality food is met
- Completes production records and temperature logs
- Greets and serves customers, ensures guests needs are met and are happy with their experience
- Manages staff at off site and in house events

Sous Chef/Manager

Elite Cuisine - 700 Maryville Center Drive St. Louis, MO 63141

March 2014 - July 2014

February 2015 - March 2017

- Maintains proper guidelines to insure food safety and freshness
- Follows standardized recipes and procedures
- Creates and executes daily menu items efficiently
- Works to insure the standard for high quality food is met
- Completes production records and temperature logs
- Greets and serves customers, ensures guests needs are met and are happy with their experience
- Coordinates team members to execute daily catering events
- Daily bookkeeping through Quickbooks
- Ordering of many products for daily operation i.e. paper product, beverages, and equipment

Prepared Foods

Whole Foods Market - 1601 South Brentwood Boulevard St. Louis, MO 63144 July 2014 - October 2015

- Maintain and follows proper guidelines to insure food safety
- Follow standardized recipe lists
- Complete daily production records, temperature logs, and prep sheets
- Lift and maneuvers boxes weighing up to 25 pounds
- Upkeep on daily cleaning and sanitation practices
- Greet and serve customers

Kitchen manager

Local Harvest Cafe - 3137 Morganford St. Louis, MO 63116 January 2009 - March 2014

- Followed proper standards for product freshness, food safety, weights and measures, refrigeration and sanitation.
 - Oversaw opening and mid shift operations, including staff assignments, creating production lists, and maintaining a safe and clean work environment
 - Received shipments of numerous food items such as fresh produce, meat, and dairy
 - Packaged and labeled products.
 - Lifted and maneuvered boxes weighing up to 35 pounds.
- Supervised, trained and developed team members in accordance with company policies and procedures.

- Staff scheduling
- Ordering of produce from local farmer

Education

Associate of Culinary Arts

L'Ecole Culinaire - 9811 South Forty Drive St. Louis Mo 63124

LaunchCode LC101

LaunchCode - 4811 Delmar Blvd, St. Louis, MO 63108

Currently Enrolled LaunchCode LiftOff

LaunchCode - 4811 Delmar Blvd, St. Louis, MO 63108

Certifications

LaunchCode LC101 - Certificate of Completion

References

Doug McKee - (314) 277-8131

Executive Chef for Elite Cuisine

Brendan Kerby - (314) 537-2847

Co-owner and Chef of Seed Sprout & Spoon

Tom Valli (314) 783-7213

Customer Computer Consultant at Microsoft Store